let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Who is known as the 'God of Cricket'?",
        answer: "C. Sachin Tendulkar",
        options: [
            "A. Virat Kohli",
            "B. Don Bradman",
            "C. Sachin Tendulkar",
            "D. Ricky Ponting"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which country won the first ever Cricket World Cup in 1975?",
        answer: "B. West Indies",
        options: [
            "A. Australia",
            "B. West Indies",
            "C. England",
            "D. India"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is the highest individual score by a batsman in a Test innings?",
        answer: "A. 400*",
        options: [
            "A. 400*",
            "B. 375",
            "C. 501*",
            "D. 380"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "How many balls are there in an over in cricket?",
        answer: "D. 6",
        options: [
            "A. 4",
            "B. 5",
            "C. 7",
            "D. 6"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which player has taken the most wickets in the history of Test cricket?",
        answer: "B. Muttiah Muralitharan",
        options: [
            "A. Shane Warne",
            "B. Muttiah Muralitharan",
            "C. Anil Kumble",
            "D. James Anderson"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What does 'LBW' stand for in cricket?",
        answer: "C. Leg Before Wicket",
        options: [
            "A. Long Ball Wide",
            "B. Leg Behind Wicket",
            "C. Leg Before Wicket",
            "D. Leg Bye Wicket"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Who was the first batsman to score a double century in a One Day International (ODI)?",
        answer: "A. Sachin Tendulkar",
        options: [
            "A. Sachin Tendulkar",
            "B. Virender Sehwag",
            "C. Rohit Sharma",
            "D. Chris Gayle"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "In which year did India win its second ODI World Cup?",
        answer: "C. 2011",
        options: [
            "A. 1983",
            "B. 2007",
            "C. 2011",
            "D. 2015"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "The Ashes is a Test cricket series played between which two countries?",
        answer: "B. England and Australia",
        options: [
            "A. India and Pakistan",
            "B. England and Australia",
            "C. South Africa and New Zealand",
            "D. West Indies and India"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Who holds the record for the fastest century in ODI cricket?",
        answer: "A. AB de Villiers",
        options: [
            "A. AB de Villiers",
            "B. Shahid Afridi",
            "C. Corey Anderson",
            "D. Rohit Sharma"
        ]
    }
];